[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In No Country for Old Men, how much does Moss pay the college boys at the Mexican border for their coat?", "correct_answer": "500 dollars", "incorrect_answers": ["200 dollars", "1000 dollars", "twenty five dollars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This country has the highest income tax rate.", "correct_answer": "Denmark", "incorrect_answers": ["Norway", "Sweden", "The US"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The comedy movie Airplane! is a spoof of several movies including Airport 75 and Jaws, but which 1957 movie did the directors claim it most closely resembled?", "correct_answer": "Zero Hour", "incorrect_answers": ["Spartacus", "Twelve OClock High", "Dr. Strangelove"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the summer of 2006, environmental consultant Mark Diacono planted the first olive grove in England. He claimed that olives can already grow in England for what reason?", "correct_answer": "Global warming", "incorrect_answers": ["Acid rain increase", "The extension of the European Union", "Acid rain decrease"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A  nine-digit number is selected at random. What are the odds that it will be your social security number (in the USA)?", "correct_answer": "1 in 1,000,000,000", "incorrect_answers": ["1 in 9", "9 in 1,000,000,000", "1 in 9,000,000,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Evapotranspiration is a term connected to which of these groups?", "correct_answer": "Plants", "incorrect_answers": ["Animals", "Water basins", "Rocks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of these actors did not star in the 1971 movie A Clockwork Orange.", "correct_answer": "Warren Brown", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael Bates", "Patrick Magee", "Malcolm McDowell"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Siberians  use reindeer to ride on.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In some animals life cycle there are several stages of development involving abrupt bodily changes. What is this biological process called?", "correct_answer": "Metamorphosis", "incorrect_answers": ["Birth", "Adolescence", "Growth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the ideal body weight for a woman with average bone structure who is 5 feet 5 inches tall?", "correct_answer": "125 pounds", "incorrect_answers": ["138 pounds", "115 pounds", "135 pounds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tiger sharks give birth to up to 12 live young at a time.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the original logo of Opel?", "correct_answer": "a zeppelin", "incorrect_answers": ["a truck", "none of these", "a lightening bolt"]}]